<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on Unbounded School</title>
    <link>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on Unbounded School</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>$1,000,000</title>
      <link>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/million/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/million/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;hero&#34; src=&#34;https://unbounded.school/images/hero/million.jpg&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;auto&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What I would do with 1,000,000 dollars is buy toys for my sister,&#xA;nice dresses and earrings for my mom, and Reeses and new shoes&#xA;for my dad. Then, I would buy lot of beautiful fabric and art materials.&#xA;Last, I would go all around the world in amazing private plane. That’s&#xA;just some things I would do with 1,000,000 dollars!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Superpower</title>
      <link>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/superhero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/superhero/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;hero&#34; src=&#34;https://unbounded.school/images/hero/superhero.jpg&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;auto&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If I had a superpower, I would have the superpower to fly really fast.&#xA;I would have that power because I think it would be amazing to fly up to&#xA;the giant clouds and get to places quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would help people with my superpower by flying up high to look for a&#xA;little girl’s doll that she lost, or saving a young boy from falling off a high edge.&#xA;I would help with anything else anyone needed. I am Scarlett the amazing superhero!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holes</title>
      <link>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/holes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/holes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;hero&#34; src=&#34;https://unbounded.school/images/hero/holes.jpg&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;auto&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the book Holes there is a boy named Stanley.  He went to school and was a&#xA;pretty big kid, and he got laughed at for that. One day, he was walking under a&#xA;bridge on his way home from school and from out of the top of the bridge, shoes fell down on&#xA;him. They were a famous baseball players shoes. The cops came by and took him&#xA;to court. They gave him the choice to go to jail or Camp Green Lake. He chose Camp&#xA;Green Lake.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Dresses</title>
      <link>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/100dresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/100dresses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;hero&#34; src=&#34;https://unbounded.school/images/hero/100dresses.jpg&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;auto&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Hundred Dresses, by Eleanor Estes. The theme is forgiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the book The Hundred Dresses, there is a girl named Wanda. She went to school like any&#xA;other normal kid, but she had been missing school. In Wanda’s class there was a bunch of kids,&#xA;but Peggy was the prettiest. Peggy’s best friend was Maddie. They did everything together.&#xA;Maddie thought she knew why Wanda was missing school. It all started on a beautiful day,&#xA;Wanda got to school and Peggy asked Wanda how many dresses she had. Wanda only had one&#xA;dress but she didn’t want to tell everyone that so she said she had one hundred, all lined&#xA;up in her closet. Everyone started asking her that every day and Maddie could tell that was making&#xA;Wanda feel uncomfortable. That was why Wanda wouldn’t come to school. Maddie felt bad and so  did&#xA;Peggy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Mile Race</title>
      <link>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/1mile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/1mile/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;hero&#34; src=&#34;https://unbounded.school/images/hero/1mile.jpg&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;auto&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I trained for a one-mile race once. Every Wednesday, I would practice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On the first Wednesday of practice, I ran two minutes and walked one minute five times.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On the second Wednesday, I ran three minutes and walked one minute four times.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On the third Wednesday, I ran five minutes and walked one minute two times.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The fourth Wednesday I ran a whole mile without stopping to walk.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I ran with some of my neighbors from Crocker Court, so we made shirts that&#xA;said Crocker Cruisers. It was a blast!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where The Red Fern Grows</title>
      <link>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/redfern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/redfern/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seaside Sanctuary</title>
      <link>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/seaside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unbounded.school/patterns/writing/seaside/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
